// TODO: Should be replaced by API calls ASAP.

const decks = [{
    "id": 1,
    "numProblems": 30,
    "desc": "Easy plus and minus",
    "flashcards": [
        {
            "id": 141,
            "problem": "1+1",
            "solution": 2
        },
        {
            "id": 2,
            "problem": "4+1",
            "solution": 5
        },
        {
            "id": 5,
            "problem": "6+0",
            "solution": 6
        },
        {
            "id": 8,
            "problem": "2+7",
            "solution": 9
        },
        {
            "id": 9,
            "problem": "0+0",
            "solution": 0
        },
        {
            "id": 12,
            "problem": "3+6",
            "solution": 9
        },
        {
            "id": 15,
            "problem": "1+3",
            "solution": 4
        }
    ]
},
    {
        "id": 3,
        "desc": "Medium plus and minus",
        "numProblems": 30,
        "flashcards": [
            {
                "id": 141,
                "problem": "1+1",
                "solution": 2
            },
            {
                "id": 2,
                "problem": "4+1",
                "solution": 5
            },
            {
                "id": 5,
                "problem": "6+0",
                "solution": 6
            },
            {
                "id": 8,
                "problem": "2+7",
                "solution": 9
            },
            {
                "id": 9,
                "problem": "0+0",
                "solution": 0
            },
            {
                "id": 12,
                "problem": "3+6",
                "solution": 9
            },
            {
                "id": 15,
                "problem": "1+3",
                "solution": 2
            }
        ]
    }
]

export default decks
